Tokyo Metropolitan Transportation Bureau Type 10-300 Train
Good morning, this is Not.Equal.Me.
As this is the first day of the call recently, we will all do our best,
Please rehearse with us today.
Please give us your best regards.
Please take care.
Please give us your best.
We will start with Last Chance, Last Dance.
May I start with the choreography of Tomita's song?
Yes.
Please listen to it. Last Chance, Last Dance.
Yes, you're all set.
We'll have it at the venue, the Member Dee House, in 30 minutes.
Yes, please.
Thank you very much for the two days of rehearsals.
We will do our best in the performance. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Great!
Mr. Chairman!
Everyone's here.
It's so delicious.
I was so impressed with the food at Domestic Fest 2021, and what a surprise to have it prepared for us.
Delicious. It's so good. It's really delicious.
They are now open at Shinogakata and Minato Mirai. I would like to go there privately.
Lovely Melody
I wonder what age it is?
What do you have?
One.
Which one?
Today's anime is a spate of anime.
Today is the day to stick together.
Today is the day for me and Hii to do our best since it's the Tokyo show. Today is the day for me and Hii to do our best since the show is in Tokyo.
Hurry up!
Lunch is a day for me to work harder.
I have a solo, so I will do my best.
In the middle.
The middle.
May I be wrong. I just said one phrase.
Quickly.
It's stable, so I can handle it.
First the sleeve. Then the middle.
No more turning.
I want you to calm down, me. I want you to calm down, me.
It's all gone in.
This way, this way.
Look behind you.
How much time do we have?
Five minutes.
Poof.
Good work, sir.
Good work.
Seventy-two police.
Czech Republic.
I'm called a lady's school.
I fall asleep in class.
Sister wants to see you, Moeiko.
Gokigenyo.
I only know how to say good-bye.
Please.
We're not quite together.
Smaller once on the count.
I'm looking at it from behind, and it looks like only Tacatacan is off.
From earlier.
Tacatacatan.
I thought it was too early.
Because this is so fast.
It's really amazing. Really great.
I'll do my best to keep my spirits up.
It's a battle.
A battle.
While everyone is dancing.
I feel like it's too early.
When it was tacatacatan, I went up rather than down.
Yes.
So, the first day.
See you.
First day. Everyone.
It's early.
First day, guys.
Early.
Good night.
Hit the chimes, hit the chimes.
Sound the chimes.
We're all in the same class now.
I'm in the same class with you.
Second year.
All right, well, be safe, and since it's your first day, don't run on the set, or the stairs, or in the back, or anything like that,
I'm sure you'll have fun, and have fun while moving around and thinking about the changes,
Let's have fun, keep the changes in mind, and have fun while doing our best.
Let's have fun, keep the changes in mind, and have fun while doing it,
Noda Kambi!
We had a big sayausa made for this tour!
Too big, isn't it?
Too big, I was surprised too!
I'm really happy that you made this big sayausa for us.
So cute!
You are my other heroine, Saya-chan!
I'm a little worried about this Saya-Usa when she finishes her tour.
I'm a little worried about her because she's not a little bit dirty.
I'd like to go around with her and make some memories.
Are you hiding? We're hiding?
Just the three of us. All three of us.
Do it, do it, do it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Here it comes, here it comes, here it comes.
Come on.
That's it!
Wow, this is fun!
I've got a fist full of them.
School's in session!
School's about to start!
Oh my God, I have to work hard, I have to work hard, I have to work hard.
I'm counting on you.
Oh!
I'll do my best.
How fast is Reckless?
He's a badass!
Today's announcements are brought to you by Natsumi Kawanako and Hitomi Suzuki from the Noemi Academy broadcast room!
But I always get super nervous when I get bald!
I know! I always feel it!
How about a game where you have to be punished if you bite something so that you don't bite it?
Oh, what's that? They make you do it?
If you bite twice, your embarrassing face will be shown on the screen.
That would be very embarrassing.
But I'll do my best not to bite. Hiiichan will do the same.
Leave it to me. Let's read without biting.
Wait, where do we start?
Let's read here, here, in full.
Read the whole thing?
Isn't that a little too school-like?
Okay, okay.
Here we go.
Before the show begins, we would like to remind everyone who is attending.
Please refrain from taking pictures with cameras, video cameras, cell phones, etc. in the venue,
Recording by cameras, video cameras, cell phones, or other recording devices is strictly prohibited.
For those with simultaneous broadcast reservations, please turn off the power and show manner mode,
Please refrain from gathering during the performance.
Turtle?
Hai. Yes, sir.
Yes.
Thank you for coming to the turtle belt.
Thank you for waiting.
Please put the camera on the monitor...
(You can take pictures only during the comment time when the “+” sign is displayed.
Please note that the penlights larger than the official goods penlights and the
Hierarchical slap penlights
Penlights that emit light at the corners and chemical lights are prohibited.
If you do not follow the instructions of the staff,
Please understand that if you do not follow the instructions of the staff, we may have to ask you to take action.
Please check the nearest emergency exits by yourself.
Did you make it?
Did you get it?
You can't see it, right?
You can't see it. You can't see it.
You can't see it.
We did it! We won.
We did it.
Yes, we did.
Oh, oh, it's already late. I have to go home.
If I don't go home before the teacher finds out, she'll get mad at me.
But you know, tomorrow is the start of a new school year.
Isn't it exciting to start a new term?
Yeah, yeah. I feel like my usual way home is sparkling.
Speaking of a new semester, there will be a class change.
I wonder who I will be in the same class with?
Huh? Who do you want to be in the same class with? Hey, hey.
It's not like that.
It's just that for five years now,
Just, for five years now,
I don't want to be in anyone's class.
Oh, that's some serious shit.
Well, I'll see you tomorrow.
Yeah, see you tomorrow. Bye bye.
Tomorrow is a new term. Class change, huh? I'm looking forward to it. Phew, new term starts tomorrow. Class change, huh? I'm looking forward to it.
But I'm worried. What if we're in different classes?
But I guess there's no use worrying about it. I'm going home early and going to bed.
Did you see it for the first time? You didn't see it, did you?
Did you see it?
It was pretty early on.
I'm going to do a star bye. I'll do a star bye.
I'll be fine. I'm so nervous. But I'm so excited.
I can do it. I can do it.
Too much fun?
All right.
I got it.
I'm so nervous.
I'm so nervous!
I'm so excited!
Thank you for watching!
Fireworks display
I wrote a letter in the Tanabata search at school.
I wrote it so that I can go to the fireworks show with the person I love.
I wonder if you'll see it?
I'll give you all my passion.
Performed by Aoi Tokyo Partner
Why
Archive of Macellia
Let's start running
Come on, the weather's fine Still piling up
I can hear the ugly
I don't care if it hurts I've got a feeling I'm in love
I'm sure you'll notice something
I've always been a thrill seeker I don't need it
Turn it off, go to your bedroom, I'm sure you'll find something
I'll catch the train.
Happiness. I'll put it on you.
Your heart Your Heart
Freezing cold, then hot.
I'm sure it will.
Even this summer.
Sometimes I notice
I notice your heart
I know you'll smile again someday
I know your heart is with me
And the result is that we'll turn
That moment when you wish you could make a mistake
Oh, my tongue is so thin, it hurts
Oh, for tomorrow's days Oh, it hurts
My love, hold my thoughts
Winter's coming for both of us, my hands will bear it
You and everything are so beautiful
It's a world I don't know
It's love.
It's you, it's you, it's you
I'm in love this summer, and the crush is impulsive
You can't force your way into my heart
That's the only thing that's dark.
I've pushed you away.
I won't lie to you about how I feel
I'm ready for the blue sky to turn to summer
I've already forgotten.
The sun is tanning.
The expression on your face, your imagination.
And all the trouble it's caused.
Oh, I've always loved you.
I've always loved you. I can't take my eyes off you.
Now love is about to begin
Ladies and gentlemen, how long will it last?
3.2.1 Go!
With a loud voice
Nighty-night
Can you tell everyone you love them more?
We'll tell them how much we love them too!
Finally tomorrow will come Tomorrow will finally come.
Don't let me see you.
Adulthood. Cute stamps.
How do you feel about tomorrow?
Did you see what I saw?
Pounding and gazing
Confidence please
With God
I've been thinking about you
My Courage
3.2.1 Go!
Congratulations on your future
Because it's you
I love you so much
I want to tell you how much I love you
In the future
Let's look at each other more
Because I love you
Mysterious vision
The world is like this again
I see the color of love, isn't it wonderful?
Ending
You like me
Congratulations!
Thank you so much for sharing your voices with us today.
Thank you so much for letting me sing with you today!
I hope you all liked me more than 5 people.
Thank you very much!
We are so happy to be able to tour like this again this year.
It is because of the support of so many people
It's because of the support of so many of you.
I am really filled with gratitude.
Thank you very much.
After this, the tour will continue as it is the first day of the tour.
If there are other chairpersons who would also like to come, please let me know.
Thank you very much.
Some of you may say that today is the last day. Today may be the last day for some of you.
But for some of you, today is the last time.
Today, Tokyo Gummistar came to our school.
They are in the same class with us as Tokyo Gummistar.
We have been in the same class for a long time.
So let's definitely see each other again.
I'm looking forward to seeing you again.
Finally, we are in the same class!
Yay!
I was so happy to be able to spend time with all of you!
Thank you so much!
That's all for now.
Thank you very much for Tokyo Gummistar!
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
That was a lot of fun.
It was a lot of fun.
So many people.
So many people came up to the top.
I was really happy.
I'm so happy.
Japanese whip?
Japanese whip
OS-1 and water
Luxury!
It's important.
Big deal.
That was fun, wasn't it?
There's more to come.
After this, we'll go to Fukushima. After this, it's Fukushima.
NEXT
Mire-chan's Fukushima
Fukushima
I'll enjoy it.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye!
It was fun!
Good morning.
Finished Saki?
That was fast.
Too late for shit.
There were a lot of night performances, weren't there?
Yeah, it was.
That means it was fun.
It was super fun.
I loved the hot solo.
It wasn't like I was nervous or anything.
But I was surprised that I was accepted.
I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it.
I can't do it. I was so worried when we were rehearsing.
That's the best counsellor I've ever had.
But I get it.
I'm totally nervous.
But he's so cute.
The screen was so cute.
Thank you very much.
I'm sure it was.
I haven't seen it.
It's definitely cute.
What do you think?
It's different. I can tell.
Because this is it.
The first day is over.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
I might be a little too sweaty.
It was fun.
See you soon.
So, the Not EcoAlmy National Tour 2024, the first day of the same class, is finally over.
Thank you very much.
And yes, the first day is over, but it means that we have finally started,
I am looking forward to spending wonderful memories and a wonderful youth with you all.
This time, we are finally in the same class...
I'm looking forward to spending wonderful memories and spending wonderful youth with all of you.
I want to deepen the distance and bond between us.
I would like to deepen my love for you all.
The penlights all over the venue were really beautiful.
I was in the Tokyo group today.
I'm looking forward to being in the same class with everyone at the next venues.
I'm really looking forward to be in the same class with you.
I'm looking forward to being in the same class with everyone at the next and next venues.
I was so excited to see the new direction that I've never seen before. or something like that.
I'm looking forward to seeing you all in the same class at the venues that will continue to grow.
I'm looking forward to seeing you all at the lectures that are currently being accepted.
We are looking forward to seeing you at the lectures we are currently accepting!
I look forward to being in the same class with you all!
So thank you very much for your time today.
Thank you very much for watching.
That's all for now, I'm Ms. Kani-san and Ms. Eko of Nottoikorumi.
I look forward to working with you all!